(Leonard:)Penny says they're having fun
working on the prototype.
(Howard:)Remember when her fun was
nightclubs and drinking games?
(Leonard:)I know. I'm lowering
the bar so slowly.
(Leonard:)This time next year
she'll have a coin collection.
(Man:)Excuse me.
(Man:)You guys interested in a free
screening of an upcoming movie?
(Leonard:)Oh. Sorry, we can't.
(Howard:)Well, hang on.
What movie is it?
(Man:)Oh, I can't tell you.
But it does star Will Smith.
(Howard:)Wait.
I bet it's Suicide Squad.
(Howard:)Let's check it out.
(Leonard:)What about the girls?
(Howard:)Penny just said
they're having fun.
(Howard:)Honestly, you want to wrap tape
around a bunch of pipe fittings
(Howard:)all afternoon?
(Leonard:)Okay, we'll take 'em.
(Leonard:)Okay.
But, I swear,
(Leonard:)if it's Will Smith
in Shark Tale 2,
(Leonard:)it better be at least as good
as the original.
(Penny:)I mean, it's crazy,
isn't it?
(Penny:)I moved here from Nebraska
to be an actress,
(Penny:)and now I'm sitting
in an engineering lab at Caltech
(Penny:)helping to build a prototype
for a high-tech guidance system.
(Bernadette:)It is crazy. It's also crazy